Once again i'm forced out to give out the official game of the year (Quick note to that one guy who put all the full stops in the subs of the last video: don't do that -thunder)
When in reality i want to give it to lootboxes
(insert... something i guess?)
First i'll be talking about all the games that didn't get game of the year
If you think i'm being unfair
that's because i am
I didn't get a single one of these games for free
First big game to come out this year was Resi VII
They finally went back to horror when every horror game got demonetized
No free ads for Capcom
Its the only video where i got permanent demonetization
and that's why you are seeing kittens. I like money
Still, it's a good change for the franchise
Previous games were way too weeb for me,
and i would never buy a weeb game
Anyways, the only game i preordered this year was Danganronpa(V3: Killing Harmony)
Spend 30 hours getting to know people who will die brutal deaths
As opposed to previous games, this one has sex scenes
Sadly, they are text only and doesn't affect the story
Makes sense, you can't make it an adult game
Never have too many genres
Prey is an Action-RPG-FPS-RPG-Stealth-Horror-Exploration Game
and it goes... ehh?
It's not all those genres that ruin it, it's the enemies
Oh a mimic attacked me again that's still cool and not annoying after 70 times
Forced to waste all my bullets on that stuff that clogs the drain
Better upgrade hacking or don't play at all
2017 was the year of the platformer
Like Cuphead
As a gamer i like it
As a professional animator, not impressed
Look at this animation i made. Took ten seconds
And Cuphead is like nine hours, so i can make all of this in like a week
Yooka Laylee isn't that good, collectathons are dead
(A) Hat in Time is great, collecathons are the future
After all the hat-based collectathons this year
it's the second best
But in terms of games where you sell your soul to the devil
But in terms of adorableness
it's number one of all time
Go fuck yourself, Kinectimals
And that's why i can't recommend it, because it gave me diabetes
Nice mods though
Are there any other good platformers?
They made a 2-D Sonic game where he can't become a werewolf
And it doesn't have Shadow so who cares?
We need a real Sonic game
It's two hours long, which is a good thing
because it's fast, like Sonic
But on the "Create your own hedgehog" you can't create a red panda and that really irritates the people
But not as much as:
Shadow of War pissed off everyone before release
Lootboxes, hottie spider
or just general anger issues
Shadow of War had something for everyone to be angry about
To reach the real ending you had two choices
Grind, or spend money
Or cheat engine (seriously, that's a good idea)
I actually finished Shadow of War
Might be my most played game this year because i had to reach the true ending
TOO BAD THIS ACCENT OFFENDS ME SO MUCH
I REALLY HATE IT
No, i'm sorry
There's a lot of hate in this community
and the only cure is laughter
One company sought to unite the people
In March the entire community came together
to make fun of Mass Effect Andromeda
We all knew something was wrong after that first gameplay trailer
Who is to blame for this?
Most of the evidence points to
not EA
You did it, guys, it's not your fault
For now
What happened?
Allegedly the writers had never talked to another human before
and the Developement Lead's parents were killed by animators
so they punished them every way they could
causing the most magical moments of 2017
enough about failures, it's a fact that the best-selling game is the best game
like the best game 2016 was FIFA
and the best game 2015 was FIFA
So let's talk about them games that got them dollars
When we saw the first trailer for Destiny 2 we all thought it was just an expansion
Kinda wish it was, because then i wouldn't have bought it
In Destiny 2 the last human settlement is attacked by
the worst video game villain of all time
"We are not so different, you and I"
Don't you dare say it
The game has this dark tone, but the commercials were all these fun, Marvel-esque
Like, compare this to a trailer
By another company to a game with essentially the same story line
The player character losses his powers for almost 10 seconds can't have tension might not buy
Lootboxes
[transcription incomplete]
Honestly thought ı am sorry you did not make good game marvel
Stick to move is Horizan Zero Dawn
Takes place in distant year of 2009
This was my 2009
Killer robots has destroyed civilization
At least they claim responsibility. We all know who realy did it
You play as a ginger that is hated by everyone
But not for that reason
It has stunning robots that make no sense in warfare and in environment look great
But this is by the same company that made Kıllzone 2
So I don't believe this what it actually looks like
And the game is called Zero Dawn
But it has dawns a lot of them BAN IT !
Best selling PS4 exclusive but sold nothing compared to PUBG
It sold billions of copies and made Mandarin the biggest language on steam
And got a guinness world record for worst optimized game
Player models do not even open their mouths
But they have fully rendered teeth worst of all
We are gonna see hundreds of PUBG clones this coming year
It's fun and it's a great lan game
But it's not my game of the year because it's not necessarily good
A lot of games failed because they were released in fall
It war a massacre
They even released 3 games on the same day
But which one is the best game. Mario Odyssey
But second place it could be Assasin's Creed leash legends the beginning
It set in hellenistic Egypt
They put it in Hela Egypt instead of Ancient Egypt because more celebrities
Spoiler alert Julius has a english accent and he dies
They used to release them annually but now they waited a year and did nothing for 12 months and on the last day and they wrote 3 letters the side quests
Have made me rage quit more times then any other games in the last years
The next game fits better in the segment
In the trailer we saw how Nazis had taken over America
And the trailer was basically all of it beat it in 6 hours on a lower difficulty
Apprently thats pretty standard
90% of that time was trying to find my way on this stupid ship
The addition with Hitler was pretty funny
But there was also
The worst FPS level in modern times
I would probably the nicer watched this game
If they haved a price in a less the a month
That actually stung Bethesda they were a lot of Swedish games this year
But let's talk about one you probably haven't heard of
The original didn't have lootboxes
So alredy this has more content
It also have a singleplayer campaign
It's terrible
You play as an officer of the Empire she is gonna switch sides isn't she?Total one eighty in a dream campaign it would and with her facing firing squad
Shouting Rebel Scum. The multiplayer progression system is so bad it pissed of governments but there is gonna be free dlc hopefully the cassino planet
Sadly, uh, hey Dice looking at this list of heroes: Phasma, Bossk where is Samuel Jackson ? Where the fuck is my main man Kit Fisto?
It's not a true Star Wars game without my main man Kit Fisto text 20 hours to get Darh Vader i don't really see the problems with that
A game needs at leat 20 hours before i reached first Chop More on that in the next segment
Foking hell this is a long game
Persone 5 is about this kid he stops in assault that turns into a
Government conspiracy so a talking cat teaches him out to steal hearts so they decided to rob a casino
It's the best RPG of the year
Not only being better than previous games in almost every single way the main character is hilarious these previous paper people didn't even react to their situation but this guy has the driest comments
Now I've only played for 35 hours so I'm still at the beginning yet even now I know I can't give it my game of the year
Because not everything is voice acted unlike Divinity 2
The original Voice actor it's a game about voice actors and their fantasy
It's a good kick starter game
Now I don't believe it either i think it is a urban legend you play as a person that's been chosen by god
Unlike other games here no one cares except for weirdos just like real life
Talk to animals and get sad when they die
Kill anyone else
And don't get sad
And that's a problem for me
I am very incompetent
I managed to get every important NPC killed
Even if they are completely safe
I need an auto play feature
Nier:Automata is a game where robots have destroyed civilization
We all know who really did this
But it has also has robot waifus
And that makes it seven hundred times better warning do not bring this game on airplane because it will make your head explode
Play as 2B and her sidekick with way less fanart
Take on an adventure and aaah
I can't spoil this game
Naah really can't I have no idea what is going on but I am feeling every emotion
Even new ones I didn't know existed
You have to beat the game twice to get the last half of the game
Was this made by a mad man ?
YEAH It's a great time
But not my game of the year because it has 26 endings
And I've only gotten 22
The rest might ruin it the correct amount of endings is five and a half
Now let's go to the 2Kings
It's been 7 years
Since the last real Mario game
Or a month according to Nintendo The story of super Mario Odyssey
Is seriously you need me to tell you what makes Odyssey original is Mario's new abilities and slavement
You enslave sentient creatures to perform tasks for you, then you KEEL THEM.
Yes, it's a bit darker than previous iterations
It even has
a Dark Souls
level.
There are, of course, magical, cartoonish worlds... and New York.
But my big question is... Bowser is trying to marry
Peach. Who is recognizing this wedding, and why is he...
...is it for tax reasons?
Or to protect inheritance? Or... *sigh*
I have too many questions. Terrible game, not recommended.
Breath of the Wild is everyone’s game of the year
Which I think is a bit unfair
It's a Zelda game, so it shouldn't be compared to non-Zelda games
The story is machines have destroyed
civilization.... *No demonitization without representation*
It's also a love story of two senior citizens
Yes, they look like teenagers but they are both over one hundred
This time Zelda has a character and a voice
They didn't give Link a voice.. Nintendo, learn from better Zeldas
Otherwise, truly, it's the biggest Zelda game ever
And that's why I can't give it my game of the year because it's open world
Being open world makes it a Ubisoft game
And no Ubisoft game can ever be in my top three
Now, finally
Number three:
Half Life 2 Episode 3
After all these years it's officially out and for free
Uhh. A-A lot less gameplay than I remember
Uhh, still very satisfying. I'm happy with this
My number two is For Honor
A Ubisoft game that did everything to keep a stable player base
[transcription incomplete]
My number two is Doki Doki Literature Club!
What I love about it is that it's a normal dating sim
and nothing else
Finally, my number one
What could be better than Half Life and For Honor?
It's pretty obvious: Microsoft released the most powerful console of all time
Just like the Atari Jaguar
They made no games for it but they did release..
Halo 3 in 4K!
It's by far the best game since 2007
In it, you finish the fight!
Against shitty normal HD
Also I lied, I got a hat in time for free
And that's Kilian Experience